<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Create a 30 Days App</string>
    <string name="tip1_name">Find your "why"</string>
    <string name="tip1_description">To fuel your motivation, understand the deeper reasons behind your goals and aspirations.</string>
    <string name="tip2_name">Create a positive environment</string>
    <string name="tip2_description">Surround yourself with positivity, whether it is through inspirational posters, uplifting music, or encouraging friends.</string>
    <string name="tip3_name">Practice gratitude</string>
    <string name="tip3_description">Reflect daily on what you are grateful for to foster a positive mindset and motivation.</string>
    <string name="tip4_name">Set deadlines</string>
    <string name="tip4_description">Assign specific deadlines to your goals and tasks to create a sense of urgency.</string>
    <string name="tip5_name">Embrace challenges</string>
    <string name="tip5_description">See challenges as opportunities for growth rather than obstacles, which can boost your motivation to overcome them.</string>
    <string name="tip6_name">Reward yourself</string>
    <string name="tip6_description">Treat yourself to small rewards when you accomplish tasks or milestones to stay motivated.</string>
    <string name="tip7_name">Stay flexible</string>
    <string name="tip7_description">Be adaptable and open to change as your goals and circumstances evolve.</string>
    <string name="tip8_name">Track progress</string>
    <string name="tip8_description">Keep a journal or use apps to monitor your progress and see how far you have come.</string>
    <string name="tip9_name">Stay inspired by role models</string>
    <string name="tip9_description">Study the lives and journeys of people who inspire you to maintain motivation</string>
    <string name="tip10_name">Practice visualization</string>
    <string name="tip10_description">Picture yourself succeeding in your goals in vivid detail to increase motivation.</string>
    <string name="tip11_name">Eliminate negative influences</string>
    <string name="tip11_description">Minimize contact with people or situations that drain your energy or enthusiasm.</string>
    <string name="tip12_name">Set personal challenges</string>
    <string name="tip12_description">Challenge yourself with new experiences or hobbies to stay engaged and motivated in different areas of life.</string>
    <string name="tip13_name">Find accountability partners</string>
    <string name="tip13_description">Share your goals with someone who can hold you accountable and offer support.</string>
    <string name="tip14_name">Stay curious</string>
    <string name="tip14_description">Cultivate a sense of curiosity and wonder about the world to stay motivated in your pursuits.</string>
    <string name="tip15_name">Keep a "done" list</string>
    <string name="tip15_description">Instead of a to-do list, maintain a list of completed tasks to see your achievements and stay motivated.</string>
    <string name="tip16_name">Set clear goals</string>
    <string name="tip16_description">Define specific, achievable goals to give yourself a sense of direction and purpose.</string>
    <string name="tip17_name">Create a vision board</string>
    <string name="tip17_description">Visualize your goals by creating a vision board with images and quotes that inspire you.</string>
    <string name="tip18_name">Break tasks into smaller steps</string>
    <string name="tip18_description">Divide large tasks into smaller, manageable steps to make progress more achievable.</string>
    <string name="tip19_name">Prioritize tasks</string>
    <string name="tip19_description">Focus on the most important tasks first to prevent feeling overwhelmed.</string>
    <string name="tip20_name">Establish a routine</string>
    <string name="tip20_description">Create a daily or weekly routine to build consistency and discipline.</string>
    <string name="tip21_name">Stay organized</string>
    <string name="tip21_description">Use calendars, to-do lists, or digital apps to organize your tasks and deadlines.</string>
    <string name="tip22_name">Eliminate distractions</string>
    <string name="tip22_description">Identify and minimize distractions to maintain focus on your goals.</string>
    <string name="tip23_name">Celebrate achievements</string>
    <string name="tip23_description">Acknowledge and celebrate your successes, no matter how small, to boost your motivation.</string>
    <string name="tip24_name">Stay inspired</string>
    <string name="tip24_description">Surround yourself with motivational quotes, books, or podcasts to keep your inspiration levels high.</string>
    <string name="tip25_name">Find a support system</string>
    <string name="tip25_description"> Share your goals with friends or family who can provide encouragement and accountability.</string>
    <string name="tip26_name">Practice self-compassion</string>
    <string name="tip26_description">Be kind to yourself when facing setbacks or challenges, and avoid self-criticism.</string>
    <string name="tip27_name">Stay healthy</string>
    <string name="tip27_description">Prioritize physical and mental health through exercise, a balanced diet, and regular sleep.</string>
    <string name="tip28_name">Visualize success</string>
    <string name="tip28_description">Imagine yourself achieving your goals to reinforce your commitment and motivation.</string>
    <string name="tip29_name">Learn continuously</string>
    <string name="tip29_description">Pursue new knowledge and skills to stay engaged and interested in your pursuits.</string>
    <string name="tip30_name">Mix up your routine:</string>
    <string name="tip30_description">Occasionally change your environment or try new approaches to prevent monotony and keep things fresh.</string>
</resources>